

Marco Maida Computer scientist



13 August 1994



github.com/marcomaida



00marcomaida00@gmail.com

About me ———

I am a computer scientist currently pursuing a PhD at Max Planck Institute for Software Systems.

I was born in Turin, Italy, and have been tinkering with computers since I have memory. In 2013, I started working professionally as a programmer. After three years, I decided to start a bachelor degree in Computer Science, while I kept working part-time as game developer. Once I graduated, I moved to Kaiserslautern, Germany, and started a Master+PhD program.

I completed all my master courses.

Languages -

L'italiano è la mia lingua madre,

I am very fluent in English,

und ich spreche auch etwas Deutsch.

Extras ———

TODO TODO

Skills

TODO

Education

since 2019	Ph.D. student Real-time Systems group	Max Planck Institute for Software Systems
since 2019	Master in Computer Science	Technische Universität Kaiserslautern
2016-2019	Bachelor in Computer Science (110/100 cum laude)	Università degli studi di Torino
2015-2016	Game dev: Software Development (30/30)	Event Horizon School
2008-2013	Diploma in Computer Science (98/100)	ITIS A. Avogadro

Experience

since 2019 Computer Science Researcher. Max Planck Institute

I am currently working in the Real-time System group. My work is focused on the certification of timeliness in safety-critical systems using formal verification (Coq) and on trace-based schedulability anal-

ysis on Linux.

2016-2019 Game developer. 34BigThings

> I worked with Unity3D and Unreal Engine on single player and online multiplayer games shipped on Steam, PS4, XboxOne, Nintendo Switch and Android/iOS. My roles covered creation of gameplays, UIs and

architectures.

2016 Freelance Unity3D developer. Teoresi, Choralia, Maserati

I worked as a freelance developer, building interactive visualization software and a learning game using Unity3D (C#) and shipping on

mobile devices and browsers.

Software engineer. 2013-2016

I worked as a software developer using C++, C/CLI, C# and SQL building software solutions for glass processing factories. In this company I covered many roles, including traveling to customers for

selling and installing our software.

Projects

Review

2016-2019 Game developer. 34BigThings

I worked with Unity3D and Unreal Engine on single player and online multiplayer games shipped on Steam, PS4, XboxOne, Nintendo Switch and Android/iOS. My roles covered creation of gameplays, UIs and

architectures.